(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T02:14:06.441403",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: To all attendees
2次販売グッズ Essentials Pack
2nd Release Merchandise: Essentials Pack
Hoshimachi Suisei Live SuperNova: REBOOT
人の世はいついつまでも
This world is forever
間違い探しばかり
searching for mistakes.
遊び飽きたら終わりよ
It's all over once you tire of playing,
鬼が出るか蛇が出るかと
Will it be an ogre or a snake that appears next?
怯えて過すばかり
Living in perpetual fear,
さみざみと一人泣く
weeping bitterly all alone.
こんな旅路を行くことが
Having to take such a journey,
人の条理とでも言うの
would you really call this the reasoning of humanity?
憂き身を窶せど
Though I plunge myself into despair,
上手くいかずに今夜もまた嘆く
nothing came of it, and I mourn again tonight.
だけどきっと
But surely,
これはパレードさ
this is a parade.
足を引きずろうとも
Even if I have to drag these feet of mine,
この滲む痛みと引き換えに有余る喜びに出会えるの
in exchange for this seeping pain, I'll find happiness in abundance.
これは愉悦なパレードさ
It's a delightful parade,
私が生きた証ばかり撒くから
I'll be scattering out the proof of my existence.
お気に召したなら共にゆこう
And if it's to your liking, we'll go together,
道連れにしてあげるわ
I'll take you along with me.
眩いばかり華やかなり
So dazzling and glorious,
知らない噂の一つや二つ
a rumor or two I wasn't aware of—
目を瞑ってあげる
I'll turn a blind eye to them.
でも譲れない大事な想いは
But these feelings that are dear to me,
歪むことなくちゃんと伝えたいの
I want to share them with you without distortion.
私は此処だよ
I'm here,
此処で生きているんだよ
it's here that I live.
貴方と同じ心臓で刻む鼓動に乗せて進むパレード
I have a heart the same as yours, and this parade travels to the beating of that heart.
どんな景色を見に行こうか
What sort of scenery shall we go looking for?
こんな私のことを信じてくれるならどこまでも行ける
Someone like me... If you think I'm worthy of believing, then I can go anywhere.
もう一人で泣いたりしないわ
I won't cry alone anymore.
そしていつの日か私と貴方の旅が終わり迎えた日には
And one day, with me, when your journey meets its end,
抱え集めてきた荷物をただ放り投げさせて笑い合おう
the luggage we've collected, we'll throw them out and smile at each other.
そんな旅路を共にゆこう
That's the kind of journey we should be on together.
人の世はいついつまでも
This world is forever
間違い探しばかり
searching for mistakes.
遊び飽きたら終わりよ
It's all over once you tire of playing,
鬼が出るか蛇が出るかと
Will it be an ogre or a snake that appears next?
怯えて過すばかり
Living in perpetual fear,
さみざみと一人泣く
weeping bitterly all alone.
こんな旅路を行くことが
Having to take such a journey,
人の条理とでも言うの
would you really call this the reasoning of humanity?
憂き身を窶せど
Though I plunge myself into despair,
上手くいかずに今夜もまた嘆く
nothing came of it, and I mourn again tonight.
だけどきっと
But surely,
これはパレードさ
this is a parade.
足を引きずろうとも
Even if I have to drag these feet of mine,
この滲む痛みと引き換えに有余る喜びに出会えるの
in exchange for this seeping pain, I'll find happiness in abundance.
これは愉悦なパレードさ
It's a delightful parade,
私が生きた証ばかり撒くから
I'll be scattering out the proof of my existence.
お気に召したなら共にゆこう
And if it's to your liking, we'll go together,
道連れにしてあげるわ
I'll take you along with me.
眩いばかり華やかなり
So dazzling and glorious,
知らない噂の一つや二つ
a rumor or two I wasn't aware of—
目を瞑ってあげる
I'll turn a blind eye to them.
でも譲れない大事な想いは
But these feelings that are dear to me,
歪むことなくちゃんと伝えたいの
I want to share them with you without distortion.
私は此処だよ
I'm here,
此処で生きているんだよ
it's here that I live.
貴方と同じ心臓で刻む鼓動に乗せて進むパレード
I have a heart the same as yours, and this parade travels to the beating of that heart.
どんな景色を見に行こうか
What sort of scenery shall we go looking for?
こんな私のことを信じてくれるならどこまでも行ける
Someone like me... If you think I'm worthy of believing, then I can go anywhere.
もう一人で泣いたりしないわ
I won't cry alone anymore.
そしていつの日か私と貴方の旅が終わり迎えた日には
And one day, with me, when your journey meets its end,
抱え集めてきた荷物をただ放り投げさせて笑い合おう
the luggage we've collected, we'll throw them out and smile at each other.
そんな旅路を共にゆこう
That's the kind of journey we should be on together.
人の世はいついつまでも
This world is forever
間違い探しばかり
searching for mistakes.
遊び飽きたら終わりよ
It's all over once you tire of playing,
鬼が出るか蛇が出るかと
Will it be an ogre or a snake that appears next?
怯えて過すばかり
Living in perpetual fear,
さみざみと一人泣く
weeping bitterly all alone.
こんな旅路を行くことが
Having to take such a journey,
人の条理とでも言うの
would you really call this the reasoning of humanity?
憂き身を窶せど
Though I plunge myself into despair,
上手くいかずに今夜もまた嘆く
nothing came of it, and I mourn again tonight.
だけどきっと
But surely,
これはパレードさ
this is a parade.
足を引きずろうとも
Even if I have to drag these feet of mine,
この滲む痛みと引き換えに有余る喜びに出会えるの
in exchange for this seeping pain, I'll find happiness in abundance.
これは愉悦なパレードさ
It's a delightful parade,
アニメにハマって
Got hooked on anime
歌いたくなっちゃった
and wanted to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
Being able to sing karaoke while watching your favorite scenes...
尊すぎて辛いっ！
is so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニソン・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find anime and game songs you want to sing!
ビーアニ宣言！
Bi-Ani Declaration!
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね♪
Get them at amusement facilities nationwide♪
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ 演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください 声出し応援OKです
Attention: Please be aware of flashing lights and that cheering is allowed during the performance.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to all visitors
本日は、星街すいせいライブ「SuperNova REBOOT」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending Hoshimachi Suisei Live "SuperNova REBOOT" today.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
最後までライブをお楽しみいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the concert to the fullest, we have a few announcements to share with you.
公演中の写真撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は堅くお断りいたします。
The use of cameras, audio recorders, and video recording equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
場内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not overexert yourself and notify a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のお客様の迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Mosh pits, stage diving, excessive jumping, throwing items on stage, and any behavior that disturbs others or disrupts the show are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください。
Please follow the rules and enjoy the show.
みんな今日持ってきてくれてるうちわもね、高く掲げすぎないように気をつけてくださいね。
Also, please be careful not to hold your uchiwa fans too high during the performance.
ありがとう。後ろの人見えなくなっちゃうからね。
Thank you. Otherwise, the people behind you won't be able to see.
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了解ください。
Additionally, cameras for streaming and photography will be operating inside the venue, and audience seats may be captured. These recordings and photos may be used for promotions, so please understand this in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#駆け巡る星街すいせい」です。
Also, the live concert hashtag is "#KakeMeguruHoshimachiSuisei".
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください。いっぱい見にいくよタグ。ありがとね、いっぱい投稿してくれて。
Please use the hashtag to get hyped. I'll be checking the tag a lot. Thank you so much for posting!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！星街すいせいでした！
Well then, it's almost time for the curtain to rise. Let's get hyped together! This was Hoshimachi Suisei!
Baby, baby, baby, baby
盛り上がり準備できてますかー！
Are you ready to get hyped?!
さて水ちゃんはここだよー！
Now, Suichan is right here!
見えてるー？ここだよー！
Can you see me? I'm right here!
おー！見つけた！見つけた！水ちゃんここだよー！
Oh! Found you! Found you! Suichan is right here!
おー、みんなだ！よく見えるー！
Oh, everyone! I can see you so well!
みんなこっちこっちー！
Everyone, over here, over here!
みんなのお手々とかうちわ見せてくださーい！
Show me your hands and your fans!
いいねー、みんなの顔よく見えるよー！
Nice! I can see everyone's faces so well!
ぬいぐるみもたくさんありがとー！
Thank you so much for all the plushies too!
すまんねー、さんざんね、奇跡願ってるだけの人生
Sorry, I've spent my whole life just hoping for miracles...
What's me? ズゥズゥズゥ ヒッチュートリック なしの街
What's me? ...A city without tricks
Wanna be free? だってまだフリーだぜ
Wanna be free? 'Cause we're still free
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Okay, tachimachi dokudanjo
Okay, immediate monologue
Listen, listen
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
歌舞け 振り切れよ
Show off, let's push the limit
Ha! Ya-ya-ya-ya-ya show time
天辺のおおなり ほらおいで
The top is here, come on, come on
夜をコンプリート オーライ
Complete the night, all right
Hell yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
だんだんノリノリで超
Gradually getting into it, super
簡単 brah, brah, brah! Pow
simple, brah, brah, brah! Pow
Emo iwa renai ain't nobody stop
It's not that, ain't nobody stop
Oh, zendo kenran gouka attention
Oh, the whole thing is gorgeous, attention
Sawagouka ishi hyouji ni
Let's get noisy, express your will
Mou jiki shougeki no koe takaraka
Soon it'll be shocking, a voice so loud
Doudou touban
Standing here in dignity
Mou garandou wa tokku no tou touta
The emptiness has long since been eliminated
Ay, ryouran ouka ode mashi da, ah
Ay, blooming cherry blossoms, it's our turn, ah
Kakkou tsuke teru tsumori wa no, no
I'm not trying to look cool, no, no
Ootomatikku ni afurechau honnou
It overflows automatically, my instincts
Notamau dan toudai no ue de hashage karei
I'm shouting it out from the lighthouse
Da-rat-a-tat-a, warning!
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Banzai asobu ge ni kotobuki
Banzai, it's time to play, so let's celebrate
Shout it out, shout it out
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Hannari kanjou doori ni hassou tobi
Following my feelings, jumping out of the box
Shout it out, shout it out
(Hey, uh)
Kuracchaina
Get addicted to it
(Hey, ha)
Rat-tat-tat-tat-tat
Mankai souin ikki ni tobikiri jump around
Blooming in full force, jumping around all at once
Look at me now
Hifu wo yaburi sou na hodo ni haneru shinzou
Tearing through the skin, the heart is pounding
Kurai gekijou teki shiyou
Exotic theater-like appearance
Ini mini mani mo gora ijou
Ini mini mani mo, it's more than expected
Kara no gora ikou
Let's go from here
Kakurenbo shiteru sono kimochi kaihou
Letting out feelings of playing hide and seek
Shakariki jimi chau
Giving it my all
Jabarabadabi kataru nima iba
Jabarabadabi, talking about the dream, a dreamer
Yashinka shitto suru you na juu su
I'm jealous of the juice
Taburakasu nakat to naccha iya
I don't want to become that, karma is near
Karuma ni itaru mae ni tayutau wa
I'm wavering
Jabarabadabi kataru nima iba
Jabarabadabi, talking about the dream, a dreamer
Yashinka shitto suru you na juu su
I'm jealous of the juice
Taburakasu nakat to naccha iya
I don't want to become that, colorful butterflies
Toiro no batafurai
The butterflies of many colors
Gozonji no doori souzoushii kodou ni
As you know, tied by a noisy heartbeat
Hoda sarete mou tomarenai
I can't stop anymore
Shoudou ni tosou shi egaita daybreak
The daybreak painted with a head-on collision
Hai kantsuu teion kyou
Piercing through the low-pitched madness
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Irei no kiken do hirui naki kakki juu man
Extraordinary danger level, energy is 100,000
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Ichika bachika aa
All or nothing, ah
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Banzai asobu ge ni kotobuki
Banzai, it's time to play, let's celebrate
Shout it out, shout it out
Na-na, na-na-na
Ready for my show
Kassai makio kosu tame ni stay
Stay to create applause
Issai gassai wasurete shout it out
Forget everything, shout it out
Ay, woah-oh-oh-oh
Migi ni hidari matomete
Gather them up left and right
Rat-a-tat-a-tat
Omoikkiri ikki ni
With all my might, all at once
Nani wa tomoare go shou wa are
Anyway, let it be known
Shout it out, shout it out
遠くで近くでそばにいるのに
Even though you're far, close, and right beside me,
僕がどれくらい知れているんだろう
I wonder how much of you I really know.
眺める空見つめる時に焦がれてる水の中で
When gazing at the sky and yearning in the water,
消えないでよ
Don't disappear!
飛ぶ度輝いて運命なのか幻なのか
Each time I fly, is it fate or an illusion?
ああ 千日数が心に咲く
Ah, a thousand days bloom in my heart,
全部のゆだんを脱ぎ捨てたい
I want to cast aside all my carelessness,
自由をあなたと抱きしめたい
and embrace freedom together with you.
同じ夢の中目覚めたのなら 掴んだ不安も眠るのに
If we woke up in the same dream, anxiety would sleep too,
ここには僕らしかいられない
but here, only the two of us can remain.
覗いた窓の外には止まり 決めた微かに響きを辿ってく
Peering out the window, tracing faint echoes outside,
あなたの総意へと帰りたい
I want to return to your thoughts.
この声はどう動いてる？ 心はここにいる？ どんな未来つながっていくんだろう
Where is this voice moving? What future awaits us?
窪みな君のサイド 沈み込む午後 いつまでそこにいてるんだろ
In the hollow of your side, sinking afternoon...
祈るたび包まれて 愛れなのか 孤独なのか
Wrapped in prayer—is it love, or loneliness?
ああ 千日数が心に咲く 誰にも言えず見つめるだけ
A thousand days bloom, gazing without words.
全部のゆだんを脱ぎ捨てたい 自由をあなたと抱きしめたい 同じ夢の中目覚めたのなら 掴んだ
I want to cast aside all carelessness with you.
僕らは宇宙の隅に生きる
We live in a corner of the universe,
ここには僕らしかいられない
where only we are allowed to exist.
覗いた窓のすぐ鳥は飛び
A bird flies right past the window I peeked out of,
決めた声少しずつ響きわたっていく
and our decided voices slowly echo outward.
あなたの明日へ還っていきたい
I want to return to your tomorrow.
僕の本当の音を聞かせてください
Please let me hear my true voice.
切った台本に縛られてずっと
Bound to a torn script all this time,
縛り付けられているこの上へ
tied down above this place,
歪んだメッセージが流れ出す
a distorted message begins to flow.
そして凍った街の壁 叩いていく
Then I knock on the frozen walls of the city.
きっと誰もただ一人で
Surely everyone, all alone,
口をつむぎながら泣いているんだ
is crying while keeping their lips sealed.
嫌いじゃない 愛してる 大嫌い 大好き
I don't hate it, I love it, I hate it, I love it.
たった思いクライの思いが溢れる
Overflowing with such heavy, dark thoughts.
戸惑い準じて去っていくこの感情は
This emotion, leaving in confusion,
音の中で初めて惹かれあうんだね
is drawn together for the very first time within the sound.
歌の中で初めて響きだすんだね
Resonating for the very first time within the song.
裂けた台本と並んだ無表情に
Beside the torn script and uniform expression,
臆病になっていたこの上へ
growing cowardly above this place,
叶わない祈りと知られざる重力に
to unfulfilled prayers and unknown gravity,
名前もイニシャルも名付けられている
names and initials have been given.
なんてどこかで言い訳が
Somewhere along the way, I made excuses,
声をつむったまま 遠い目になってるんだ今さら
keeping my voice closed, with a distant gaze now of all times.
笑えない景色を 信じて そう好き
Trusting a scene I can't smile at, so much so...
やん なるくらいの 燃え盛る
burning to the point of getting sick of it,
今日も街は去っていく 森を 足が 飛び上がる 宙 を 知ってる
today too the town leaves, knowing the void where feet leap into the sky.
何もかも 半端で ほかして
Leaving everything half-done,
歩いて 生きていく
I walk and live on.
知りたい 知りたい そうだよ そうだよ
I want to know, I want to know, that's right, that's right.
嫌いじゃない 好きじゃない 全部が 一つが
Not hate, not love, everything as one.
戻りたい 戻りたい どうしたい どうしての
I want to go back, I want to go back, what do I want, why?
聞かせない 聞かせて
Don't let me hear, let me hear...
伝えたい 愛してる 大嫌い 大好き
I want to convey it: I love it, I hate it, I love it.
たった思いクライの 思いのサイズまで
To the size of that heavy, dark thought,
今日もまだ 疼いてる この感情が
today too, this emotion aches,
音の中で初めて 惹かれあうまで
until we are drawn together for the first time within the sound.
あなたのその胸で 響き出すまで
Until it resonates within your chest.
愛してる 大嫌い
I love it, I hate it.
そうだよ 大好き
That's right, I love it.
綺麗だな
It's so beautiful...
盛り上がってますね
Everyone's getting so hyped!
ということで星街すいせいライブ「Supernova」といよいよ始まりましたー!
And with that, Hoshimachi Suisei Live "Supernova" has finally begun!
皆さんびっくりしたんじゃないですか ぼうとうでね
Weren't you all surprised? Right at the beginning...
ねえ、一瞬
Hey, for a second,
どこにいるかわかんなかったんじゃないかな？
you didn't know where you were, right?
わかんなかったね。
You didn't know, huh?
あれ?出てこない、出てこないじゃん?あれ?って思ったかな？
Did you think, "Wait, she's not coming out?"
あの端っこのね、あの、あそらへんの人はね、
Those people on the edge over there,
「うわ!」ってなったことと思いますけれども。
probably went, "Whoa!"
さあ、ありがとうございます。
Now then, thank you very much.
まずは自己紹介からね、いきたいと思いますよ。
First of all, let's start with self-introductions.
水星の如く現れた星の原石、バーチャルアイドルの星街水星です!
Like a comet, a rough diamond of a star, I'm virtual idol Hoshimachi Suisei!
水ちゃーん!
Suichan!
元気だね、君たち今日も。
You guys have a lot of energy today too.
え、でもさ、まだいけるんじゃない？
Um, but still, don't you have more in you?
じゃいくよ! 水ちゃんはー!
Then here we go! Suichan is--!
できるよなしかー!
You can do it, right?!
さてさて、今回のライブはですね、
Now then, for this live show,
去年行いました武道館公演の「日」として、あのセトリとかはね、結構あの似てるんですけど、
as a follow-up to the Budokan concert last year, the setlist and things are quite similar, but
2曲目がもうすでにね、前回と違いましたね。
the second song was already different from last time.
ね? あ、じゃあ、けっこうなんか変わってたりするのかな?
Right? Ah, so maybe quite a bit of it changed?
とか言って全然変わってなかったり。
Or maybe it didn't change at all.
まあ、ただ一つ言えるのは、このKアリーナという会場で、やりたかった演出とかもうレーザーバチバチとかも、演出がもうもりもりになってるんで、めちゃめちゃグレードアップしてるんで。
Well, but one thing I can say is that at this K Arena venue, the staging I wanted to do, like blazing lasers, the production is so packed, it's tremendously graded up.
で、私自身もたくさん練習してきましたんで、ダンスとかね。ちょっと頑張ってきたんで。
And I myself have practiced a lot too, like dancing. I worked hard on it.
そういう去年からパワーアップした姿をおおみせできればなと思って、はい、このライブとなっております。
Hoping to show you how I've powered up since last year, yes, this is what this live show has become.
さて、今回もですね、え、いつもの通りバンドさん引き連れております! バンドさん!
Now then, this time as well, um, as always, I've brought the band along with me! Band members!
ちょり、リハの動画とかをショートで投稿させてもらってるんですけど、
I've been posting rehearsal videos in shorts,
気づいた人いるよね?
some of you noticed, right?
今回はストリングスさんがいらっしゃいます! ストリングスさん!
This time, string players are here! String players!
もう、かっちょいいんだからストリングス入るだけでね。
Live music is just great with strings added.
ストリングスって何か知ってる? あれでしょ、あの、バイオリン...
Do you know what strings are? That, you know, violin...
今日しか聞けないライブアレンジをね、バンドさんがたくさん、たくさん作ってくださいましたので。
The band made so many, many live arrangements that you can only hear today.
もうしょっぱなからビビデバのね、もうストリングス入ったバージョンがかっこよすぎてアギトアギトになっちゃいましたね。
Right from the start, the version of Bibideba with strings was so cool I went wild.
さて、そしてそして、残ねんながらここにこられなかった星読みたちがいます。
Now then, and and, unfortunately there are Hoshiyomis who couldn't come here.
ここに、ここにこられなかった星読みたち、
To those Hoshiyomis who couldn't come here,
画面の向こうの君たち見せたかったよと言っているやつお前おるやないか!
you guys on the other side of the screen, isn't there someone saying "I wanted to see you" right there!
ちょっと待てかね、
Wait a minute,
なんかここらへんになんか、あ、なんか、ここにいるぞ、あ、なんか見える、見ているよ、あ、
around here, something... someone is here, oh, I can see them, I'm watching, oh,
いえい、俺はここにいるぞ。
yay, I am right here.
行きたかった、あ、吊るされてます号泣。
Ah, I wanted to go, ah, I'm hung up crying.
悲しいな、ニューヨークからこんにちは、あ、ニューヨークからこんにちは。
How sad, hello from New York, ah, hello from New York.
え、気になるよ。
Um, I'm curious.
海外星読みの皆さん、すごい!
Everyone reading stars overseas, amazing!
え、海外星読みではない皆さん、
Um, everyone who is not overseas Hoshiyomis,
すごい!
amazing!
素晴らしい! もうどっちも素晴らしいですね。
Wonderful! Both are wonderful.
はい、ということで、配信の方もですね、たくさんファンさしますので、寂しくさせませんからね! 絶対最初から最後まで全部見てくださいね! はい、ばちこーん!
Right, so, for the stream as well, I'll be giving lots of fan service, so I won't let you feel lonely! Be sure to watch everything from start to finish! Right, bang!
ではでは、ライブの感想はハッシュタグ「駆け巡る星町サイ」でたくさんポストしてください! ポスト?
Well then, please post lots of your thoughts on the live show with the hashtag #KakeneguruHoshimachiSai! Post?
ツイートだよな!
It's a tweet!
ツイートだな、まったく、台本はいつまでも「ポスト」って書いてあるんだから。おかしいな。
It's a tweet, really, the script always says "post". Weird.
さて、YouTube、TikTokでご覧の...
Now then, for those watching on YouTube, TikTok...
タダで見ているあなたたち
Those of you watching for free,
3曲までよ？
up to three songs, okay?
タダで見れるのは
Being able to watch for free...
代わりにね、いてくれて。ありがと。
Thanks for being here instead.
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは
Everyone who wants to get even more hyped together,
概要欄から配信サイトへレッツ・ゴー！
head to the streaming site via the description box, let's go!
レッツ・ゴー！
Let's go!
盛り上がる準備できてますか？次いじゃっていいですか？
Are you ready to get hyped? Can we move on to the next one?
リブートしたスーパーノヴァ、全身で浴びてください！
Bathe in the rebooted Supernova with your whole body!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。 ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.